[♪ rock music playing]
[Noel, in Japanese] Currently,
I'm en route to Sedona,
the final destination of this summer trip.
I have two objectives.
One, to prepare a warm welcome
for the six members,
who will be coming
at the end of their trip.
And two…
Travis Japan was approved
for a ten-day vacation!
-[Genta] Whoa!
-[Umi] What?
I have one question though.
Noel, what will you be up to?
[Genta] That's a great point. Yeah.
-Are you joining either groups?
-I will wait for your arrival in Sedona.
-Waiting?
-You'll be waiting?
I will be in special training.
-Training?
-You're going to train?
Wait a minute.
You have to train by yourself?
[exclaims, in English] Thank you.
[Noel, in Japanese] Tacos are a dish
that represents the American Southwest.
I want to serve it to the other members
upon their arrival in Sedona.
Yum.
Once again, I find myself in Sedona.
[in English] Brian!
[narrator] Sedona, Arizona.
[Noel, in Japanese] I already know
which taco truck I want to learn under.
Brian! I'm Noel!
-Good to see you again!
-[in English] Yeah. Nice to see you.
Do you remember me?
-Yes, I remember. Yeah, yeah. Yay!
-Yeah? [laughs]
-I'm pleased to meet you again.
-Okay, but you been in Japan?
-Yes. And I come back here… learn taco.
-Okay.
Are… You wanna work today?
You working tomorrow?
Today, and tomorrow,
and the day after tomorrow, and…
-Let's go. Let's get it. I love it.
-Got it. Let's go! [exclaims, chuckles]
[♪ upbeat music playing]
[narrator, in Japanese]
It's the special summer break
Noel organized
for the Travis Japan members.
At the foot of the Rocky Mountains
where the desert winds blow
lies the real America
the members have yet to see.
The Travis Japan members except for Noel
divide up into two groups
and head to their final destination:
Sedona, Arizona.
The trip is coming to a close.
Finally, it's time for Noel to welcome
the members in Sedona, their destination.
Travis Japan
SUMMER VACATION!! IN THE USA
-[exclaiming] Uniform?
-Yeah, I got it. Hold on.
What is your size?
-Bam! Bam!
-[laughs]
-How cool? So cool.
-There you go, bud. Yeah, yeah.
-Yeah. Can I change it?
-You gonna put it on?
-Can I change into uniform?
-Yeah, yeah.
How's it?
-Perfect.
-[chuckles]
Perfect. Let me see you. Perfect.
-Thank you so much.
-Perfect.
-So, I'm gonna ask you about the…
-Okay.
So what is the specialty?
What is the secret of your taco?
Because it's an organic taco?
[Brian] So, these aren't original recipes,
you know?
-You don't know.
-That is your special dish?
I'm American-Caucasian, you know,
so this is Mexican food…
Uh-huh.
…but you learn kind of to do it
sort of a new modern way.
Uh-huh.
So, we got rid of all
the poisonous stuff like
different seed oils and things like that.
There's no sugar.
-Really? Uh-huh.
-There's no seed oils in there.
Um, there's a lot
of gluten-free options and stuff.
-So, everything is specific.
-Wow.
-So, the buffalo you season a certain way.
-Oh. Hmm.
The fish you batter a certain way,
you fry it for a certain amount of time.
Uh-huh.
It's a lot of information,
but you're a smart guy. You'll learn fast.
There's a lot to take in.
[stammers] I need to learn everything?
Yeah, you're gonna need
to learn everything.
-[chuckles] Is it?
-But you can also learn while we work.
-Okay. I'm getting a bit excited.
-Okay.
-Yeah.
-[chuckles] Okay.
-Yeah, come on.
-Okay.
-So, this is the setup, okay?
-Uh-huh.
So, we have all the cold foods
-kind of here.
-Mm-hmm.
So, when you have the tacos cooked,
you'll bring them down here
-to finish it.
-Okay. Uh-huh.
So, we got a lot of stuff to train you on.
-I got steak tacos.
-Steak taco.
-Chicken tacos we'll start with.
-Chicken taco. Uh-huh.
So, there's a lot of different tacos,
but when they're all ready,
you come over here.
And that's where you put, like,
guacamole and stuff, you know?
-Okay. Got it.
-So, we'll start right there.
I need to… [stammers] I'm gonna make…
I'm gonna make taco?
-Just take it slow.
-Uh-huh.
-Do you wanna go? Are you ready?
-Yes.
-Let's do it.
-Yes. Just a moment, please?
Yeah.
-Yes, I'm ready. Let's go.
-[laughs]
-Start with the tortillas.
-Okay, start with…
-And be very careful with the oil.
-Okay, got it.
-In here?
-Top one. Top one.
-Ah, top one.
-No, the top one.
-Top one.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah. You're good.
-So, grab some out of there.
-Yeah.
Yeah--
-Two of them.
-Two. Perfect.
So, just put it, yeah,
just on the one side, and then just…
-Side.
-…yeah, and then rub it a little.
-Perfect.
-Okay.
[Brian] Boom. Next. Same.
-Boom.
-[Noel] Boom.
Yep. And then you can take this,
and kind of, like, pat it a little bit.
-That's… yeah. That's fine. Perfect.
-That fine?
[Brian] When you're ready,
if you wanna flip it, yeah.
-[exclaims]
-[Brian laughs]
-[Brian] Perfect.
-Perfect.
-This one?
-Uh-huh.
[exclaims] Okay.
[Brian] Yeah.
-Uh, wait.
-Then you wait, yep.
-Steak.
-Yeah, yeah.
Oh.
[in Japanese] Is this about right?
[in English] Is it less or…
Maybe just a li… Maybe just a little more.
Little more.
-Perfect.
-Okay.
Chicken.
[exclaims]
Like this?
[Brian] Yeah, perfect.
-Yeah, perfect. Yeah, perfect. Yeah.
-How's it? Perfect? Oh, perfect.
I'm not helping you.
-First…
-You remember.
-First, for steak, we need onion.
-Yeah.
Right, maybe.
Just… here.
Onion. Onion.
[Brian] Perfect.
-It's too much? No?
-No, that's good.
That's good. And…
[Brian] If you do something wrong,
I'll yell, "Stop."
-Okay, got it.
-[chuckles] So, your onion, and then…
And next, onion and, bro, what do you…
what do you call it?
-Cilantro. Yep.
-Cilantro.
Cilantro.
-In Spanish and in English it's the same.
-Uh-huh.
-Same. Cilantro.
-Cilantro.
-Cilantro. Cilantro.
-[Brian] Yep.
Uh, for this one.
[Brian] Correct.
What, how do you call it?
-Pico de gallo.
-Pico…
-[speaks Spanish]
Pico de gallo.
[Brian] Yep.
-[Noel] Yep.
-[Brian] Pico de gallo.
Perfect. So, yep.
Both?
This one for the steak.
This for the chicken.
Okay. Pour one white cashew.
-Cashew crema, yep.
-Cashew cream.
[exclaims]
-Like this?
-Not bad. Perfect.
-Okay.
-Not bad.
-Next one.
-And then you get this one.
[exclaims]
-That's a little bit much.
-Little bit much?
-A little bit much. It's okay, though.
-Too much? Okay.
There you go. And then you kind of… Boom.
-Boom. Oh!
-Perfect. Perfect.
[exclaims]
-Yep. And sometimes-- Perfect.
-I'm done?
Sometimes with one finger…
Take one finger. And just kind of…
[Brian] You just kind of…
-Yep. Perfect. That's it.
-That's it? That's it?
[Brian] That's it.
-Boom.
-Oh!
How does it look?
-Uh, um, so-so. [laughs]
-[laughs]
Okay. This is my first tacos!
[Noel, in Japanese]
I love learning new things.
It's fun to try my hand at something
I've never done before.
My taco-making training has just begun.
I hope the tacos will turn out
scrumptious, and everyone enjoys them.
[Noel, in Japanese] Now, to pick
the perfect wine to pair with the tacos.
[in English] Hello.
-How are you?
-I'm great, and you?
-Good. Welcome to D.A.
-I'm Noel.
-Nice to meet you. I'm Jenna.
-Nice to see you.
So, uh…
You interested in doing a flight?
-Yes, yes. I…
-Yep? All right.
So, we do have a couple options.
We got our ranch flight, that's our usual.
Uh-huh.
We also got a walking tour flight too,
so I can get you started here
with your first pour,
and if you wanna walk around the property.
-Really? Can we do this?
-Yeah.
-Absolutely.
-Thank you so much. I'd like to do this.
You want to walk around the property?
-I'll show you where these grapes…
-Can we?
…are grown right over here,
right in front.
-So, this is Syrah.
-Uh-huh.
[Jenna]
This is one of our biggest plots here.
-[Noel] Biggest plots? In this area?
-[Jenna] Mm-hmm.
…a river right behind
these big trees here.
Wow.
So, we don't have to water these too much.
-My member must love it.
-[laughs]
Yes. [chuckles]
Good. I hope they do.
-So, we harvest…
-Uh-huh.
These guys, they do everything by hand.
-It's very organic.
-[Noel] By hand?
-Oh.
-[Jenna] They hand clip everything.
So, our harvest is gonna be
in late August, early September.
-Uh-huh.
-[Jenna] So, very soon.
-So soon, yes, yes.
-[Jenna] Yes, very soon.
-On this… the end of this month? Oh!
-[Jenna] Mm-hmm.
So, how do you make the wine?
[Jenna] So a fun thing that I have here is
the Tannat, is a dark, earthy red, right?
Right, right, right.
[Jenna] If they keep the skins on,
and they age it in oak,
it's gonna be a red wine.
That's our smoky red
that I was telling you about.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But if they pull the skins off,
-you're gonna get…
-The skin's off that one.
Rosé.
-Yep, so even though it's a dark, earthy…
-Uh-huh.
-But without the skins.
-With all the skins off,
you get all of the beat in this one.
So, this is…
-You wanna try it in both forms?
-Uh…
Rosé and Red?
-This one. Yeah.
-This one?
Ah! [sighs]
[Jenna] That's the one that's closest
to the campfires.
Cheers.
-Smoky.
-Mm-hmm.
-I'm a camper, so that's why I love it.
-Oh!
-You like it? I love it too.
-I love it so much.
I want my members to drink it.
[in Japanese] The members who camped out
will be delighted with this wine.
I hope they get it.
-[person] Okay, so I can teach you…
-[Noel] Yeah.
-…how to make like guacamole. Yeah.
-Guacamole. Yeah, okay.
[narrator, in Japanese] Juan shows Noel
how to make guacamole,
which is an avocado-based sauce.
[in English] So, I can grab this knife
and then cut like half cilantro.
-Cilantro.
-Yeah.
These ingredients.
-So, avocados…
-Avocado…
-…like fresh avocados. Organic avocados.
-Uh-huh.
-Limes. Yes.
-Limes, yeah.
-And a couple onions.
-Oh! Onion.
-Yeah. Do you wanna try it?
-Yes.
So, okay. Be careful, bro.
[♪ slow guitar music playing]
You're doing great.
-How you feel this week?
-Uh… [stammers]
Making taco and then making burritos.
So, really difficult but it's really fun.
Nice. Congratulations, Noel.
Yeah, thank you.
And I need four onions, okay?
-Four onions. Okay.
-Yeah.
Yeah, so, you need to cut it in half…
-Mm-hmm.
-…and, like, you need to put these.
[Noel exclaims]
-Be careful, okay?
-[Noel] Uh-huh.
It's gonna be little… a noise.
Like… strong. One, two, three.
-There we go.
-[in Japanese] Neat.
It chops the onion instantly.
-[in English] Okay, you need like… push.
-Cut.
-Be careful. Okay.
-Okay.
-For here?
-Yeah, you need to grab the container.
-Just here?
-Yeah, and…
-Okay. Three, two, one.
-Strong.
-Three. There we go. You got this.
-Oh!
[chuckles]
-So now…
-[in Japanese] How neat.
-[in English] Wow. Cool.
-There we go, Noel.
-[in Japanese] This is amazing.
-[in English] Yeah, that's really good.
So, take him off this for…
-Jalapeños pepper.
-Jalapeño. Uh-huh.
-And you can throw away these juices.
-Oh! Jalapeño.
-It's mixed.
-Yeah. Sounds great.
-Right?
-Yep.
Okay, so, now I need the ingredient…
-the special ingredient. Okay?
-[exclaims]
-You can-- You can--
-Okay, just be half.
Yeah, perfect.
[in Japanese] Oh! Perfect halves.
-[in English] So quick. You're so quick.
-[Juan] Yeah. [laughs]
-I'm gonna be like you. [chuckles]
-[chuckles]
-One day maybe you'll…
-One day, yeah.
You'll be better than me.
Only one week is not enough…
-[laughs] …to be… as you.
-Exactly.
[Juan] Everything.
I do it?
Mash everything well. You need mash, mash.
Mash. Mash.
[in Japanese] Wow!
It's starting to look like guac.
I didn't expect this, but…
my hands are shaking.
They're that sore. Wow.
Ta-da. Fresh guac is ready to serve!
[in English] This is
really natural guacamole.
[exclaims, in Japanese]
This looks delicious.
[in English] Look.
-Did it!
-This is for you. You did it.
You did a special guacamole.
-Cheers. Cheers.
-Cheers. [chuckles]
Mmm.
That's really good, right?
-Everyone loves it. Yeah.
-You can taste everything.
-Mmm.
-Oh my…
-My goodness.
-Mmm.
[Noel, in Japanese] What drink to enjoy
with Mexican cuisine but tequila?
-[salesperson 1, in English] Welcome in.
-I have a plan for taco party.
-[salesperson 1] Oh.
-I got the perfect solution.
Yeah, so… [stammers]
What is your recommend to…
Yeah, you know. For the…
Well, with a taco party I think
you gotta bring a little tequila with you.
-So, I'll… I'll take you over…
-Tequila. Yes!
-…and I'll show you the tequila now.
-Really? Thanks so much.
-[♪ rock music playing]
-Ah! Here? What is that?
So this is where all our tequila
will be located.
Cool. Cool, cool.
So, we have a couple of different options
that we can go over.
That way you can find the right one
for your party.
-Mm-hmm.
-We're gonna have a tequila blanco.
-Blanco?
-Unaged. Distilled. Bottled.
-Easy for margaritas, tequila sunrise…
-Okay. Uh-huh.
-…shots, anything. [chuckles]
-Easy to drink. Yeah.
-Then we have a tequila reposado.
-Reposado.
This will be aged.
This will be a seven-month tequila.
-Mm-hmm.
-It'll be aged in American and French oak.
-Oh.
-Then they blend that batch together
and that's what you get right here.
-Okay.
-Reposado translates to "rested".
-Rested? Rested. Oh! Rested.
-Rested in a barrel.
-This one, we partner with Viva México.
-Viva México.
So, they are a top five-rated
tequila distillery…
-Uh-huh.
-…over the last ten years.
-One of the best ones that you can get.
-Huh.
These are double-distilled in copper pots.
-[Noel] Mm-hmm.
-So these are a whole lot of fun.
This is my personal favorite.
[Noel] It must be.
-Uh, I can't choose one. [chuckles]
-[chuckles]
-I can't.
-You can't choose one?
All right, well,
if I was gonna recommend one…
Uh-huh?
If you really wanna be
the star of the party,
-I would do the extra añejo.
-Extra añejo. Okay.
It's my rarest piece.
Four… Less than 4% of tequilas
ever make it to that age.
That's gonna make you
really popular at the party.
-Yeah.
-[chuckles]
-You wanna taste it?
-Yeah.
Let's do it.
[Noel, in Japanese]
I'm here to sample strong liquor.
[in English] Look at the beautiful color.
[in Japanese] Oh, what a pretty color.
[in English] Beautiful. So beautiful.
-There you go.
-Oh!
Oh! Oh!
Smells so good.
It's delicious.
[sighs]
[in Japanese] Bottoms up.
[in English] Amazing.
-Life-changing. [chuckles]
-Life-changing.
Life-changing experience. Wow.
-Thank you. Uh…
-You're welcome.
I'm gonna choose this one.
-You gotta take this one home.
-Yeah.
[no audible dialogue]
[♪ music ends]
[Noel] Some of the members
don't handle alcohol well.
That's why the taco truck business
is going to teach me how to
make fruit juice their way.
-Hi.
-Hi. Hi, I'm Kee.
-Kee? Noel.
-Nice to meet you.
-Thank you, Ms. Kee.
-Nice to meet you. Are you ready
for some watermelon fresca?
-Yes, please. Yes, I'm ready.
-Okay. Let's do it.
[Kee] So what we're gonna start with is,
grab your watermelon.
-Uh-huh. Okay.
-And we're gonna take our knife. Here.
'Cause we wanna be able to see
the pink part of the watermelon. Yep.
-Like this?
-Perfect. Did you get both sides?
-Both sides.
-Okay.
[Noel exclaims]
With it on one side, we're now gonna
cut the skin off of the watermelon.
So we're gonna just take our knife…
-[exclaims]
-…and we're going to cut…
-just like that.
-Okay.
-All the way around. Yep.
-Okay, red surface.
Oh!
-So fresh. Fresh, fresh.
-It is so fresh. You can smell it, right?
-Yeah, yeah. It smells… Nice scent.
-It smells so good?
-[Kee] Here we go.
-[Noel] Here we go. Here we go.
[in Japanese] These are
some chunky pieces of watermelon.
[in English] Yep.
-Nice.
-And once we cut it into smaller pieces…
-Uh-huh.
-…like this…
-Then put it in.
-Just put it right in to the container.
-Okay.
-Okay. There you go.
[Noel, in Japanese] Amazing.
There are so many pieces!
I love this.
[in English] Cut a little piece. Taste it.
Taste the watermelon?
-Mmm.
-Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
[Kee] And next we're going to add
our fresh mint.
[Noel] Fresh mint.
And then, up next we have our limes.
Oh! Limes.
So what we're gonna do is,
we're gonna stick our lime here.
Close it.
-And we squeeze it…
-Squeeze it.
…to get all the juice out.
Oh! Cool.
-And then it's… And grab another one.
-Okay.
[Noel strains]
[in Japanese] This takes
a lot more strength than I expected.
[in English] Okay. Lots of lime juice.
[Noel] Yes.
-All of them? I do? Okay.
-All of them. Yes.
I'll do my best for my members.
Yeah.
-Okay.
-Okay?
-Yes.
-Four scoops.
Four scoops. Okay.
-One scoop.
-One.
One.
[in Japanese] I can put a lot in here.
Two.
Three.
Last one, last one.
-Four! Okay.
-All right.
-Done with the monk fruit. Okay.
-Monk fruit.
[Kee] Up next,
we're gonna add our fresh water.
-Okay.
-Okay?
-Okay. Here you go.
-Okay.
-Now we get to mix it all up.
-Mix.
-Oh!
-[chuckles]
-Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
-Huge.
-Huge. Uh-huh.
-It's five feet.
Okay, so this is called
an immersion blender.
-Immersion one.
-Okay?
-[exclaims]
-[Kee] So good!
[Noel] It's getting to be juice!
[Kee] Yeah, it is.
-It's so heavy. [grunts]
-I told you it's heavy.
-Are we ready?
-Yep.
-Okay. One… two, three.
-Two, three.
-There you go! Wow!
-[exclaims]
[in Japanese] Incredible!
-[Kee, in English] Perfect. Mm-hmm.
-Perfect?
-And now we're gonna take this spoon…
-Push it?
-…and we're gonna push it down.
-Okay, okay.
Just a little bit.
[in Japanese] How cool.
This is satisfying.
You have to really push down.
-I'll put the filter right next to him.
-I bet you this pulp is tasty too.
-[in English] Yes, yes, yes.
-Let's see.
-[exclaims]
-[chuckles]
It must be tasty! It must be delicious.
One. Grab one more.
[whistles]
Two straws.
-Cheers!
Mm-hmm.
-High five.
-So good.
-You did so good.
-Mm-hmm.
-[exclaims]
Love it. love it.
-Refreshing. Mm-hmm.
-Mmm.
[sighs]
-Good job.
Thank you so much.
[♪ gentle guitar music playing]
[Noel, in Japanese] I want to prepare
a proper welcome for everyone,
complete with beautiful tableware.
-[in English] Hi. Morning. I'm Noel.
-[salesperson] Hi.
-I'm Kathy.
-Good to see you.
Uh, I'm looking for the… that tray of a…
[stammers] I'm gonna have taco party.
-Oh! How fun.
-Yes.
And I need to… I need a… You know?
-I know exactly what you want. Mm-hmm.
-Oh! Really?
I follow you.
-[exclaims]
-Taco party.
[exclaims]
-This one exactly what I needed.
-Mm-hmm.
Amazing.
Oh!
[in Japanese] This one's cute too.
[exclaims]
These are authentic Mexican-style
party plates.
[in English] The day, it's gonna be
a kind of holiday for us.
[laughs]
Okay. Could I have… Could I have both?
Both? Yes.
[♪ gentle piano music playing]
[Noel, in Japanese]
I'm having loads of fun.
It keeps me going when I think about
people enjoying dishes and drinks
I prepared with my very own hands.
It's a labor of love.
But that's what makes me look forward
to the members' smiles.
[♪ music ends]
[Noel, in Japanese] Lastly, Brian checks
the quality of my tacos.
It was nerve-racking, I admit.
But I had plenty of practice,
and more importantly,
I want everyone to enjoy delicious tacos.
[in English] Yep.
You wanna do one California burrito?
-Yes.
-With the steak.
So grab… You know where everything is.
Oh, yes. Yeah. I know everything,
-because I work here.
-You know everything.
-I'm not looking.
-[laughs]
Quit staring at me.
You've learned a lot over the week…
-Yeah.
-…and I trust that you got it.
-Okay. And…
-Okay.
Here.
Okay… Wait a minute.
-It's gonna be a really, like, nice color.
-Oh! Nice color.
-[Brian] Nice color.
-[Noel] Yeah.
Do you know the best timing?
[Brian] It all… This is… That is perfect.
Oh! It's… it looks like breathing.
-This is how you do it.
-[chuckles]
Almost.
-[Brian] Boom.
-[Noel] Boom.
-Flip. Cool.
-Boom.
Let's fill.
Okay.
One and two.
Three.
-Perfect. Perfect.
-[chuckles] Perfect. Perfect.
This too much?
-Okay. Cheese. Yes.
-[Brian] Some cheese.
Boom.
[Noel] Oh! It's gonna be so tasty.
-Uh…
-[Brian] Carry it down.
Go, go, go.
-[Brian chuckles]
-[Noel pants]
-First of all…
-You know… You know it all.
[laughs]
-Pico. You good?
-This one?
You're good.
-Put a little more.
-A little more? Okay. Thank you.
And then you got this.
-Boom.
There you go.
Perfect.
And we can roll it.
Then you roll it.
Yeah, get it ready to roll on there.
So…
[in Japanese] Oh, no, I hear cracking!
-[in English] This is hard.
-You got a lot better already.
Grab that. You got it.
Got it. Flip.
-There you go. Thank you.
-Boom.
-You got better.
-Yeah.
-Better?
-Thank you! [sighs]
-Yeah, you know.
-You're official.
-Official?
-You're official. [laughs]
-Real? Official. [laughs]
Yeah, so, how… How is it?
-How's the size? Perfect?
-It's perfect.
-That's perfect.
-Oh!
-Much better than before? [laughs]
-A lot better than your first day.
-First day, I really was… You know?
-I was embarrassed.
-Embarrassed.
-Don't say that. [laughs]
-Okay.
Thank you.
Burrito!
I'm so relieved.
-You got it?
-May I try it?
Yeah, go ahead.
-Who made that?
-Yeah, yeah, yeah, I made it.
Oh, double meaning. I made it.
[in Japanese] Digging in.
-Yum!
-[in English] Not bad. Not bad.
[exclaims]
-I'm gonna cry.
-Mmm.
-How is it?
-It's good.
-Good! Thank you!
-That's freaking good. All right.
[sighs]
-We… Now we need something to drink.
-Yeah. Yes, yes.
[♪ upbeat music playing]
[♪ music continues]
[Noel, in Japanese] I can't wait
to hear about everyone's trips.
Never before have I
missed everyone this badly.
[♪ music ends]
-[Chaka] We're meeting up at a food truck?
-[Shizu] Apparently.
-Today?
-Is that it? It's a food truck for tacos.
-You're right. It says "tacos."
-Hey, guys!
-[Chaka] Tacos to tacos.
-Huh?
-No way!
-[Noel] How've you been?
-What're you doing there? Noel!
-Why are you in the truck?
-It's been a while! [laughs]
-[Chaka] What're you doing?
-I'm so happy to see you guys!
-It's been, like, what? One week?
[in English] Hey. So, can I get a…
-tacos, please?
-[in Japanese] No, no, no.
-Why? What's this about?
-What're you doing?
-Sorry, sorry, sorry.
-What? What're you doing?
-Why are you in the truck?
-A lot happened.
-A lot happened?
-We'll find out later, yeah?
-I… took up a part-time job.
-[Umi] Right?
-[Shizu] That's cool.
-[Umi] A part-time job?
If that's true,
then I feel really terrible.
-Over here, yeah?
-Yep.
-Come this way, please.
-Oh, okay.
-You went on a journey, huh?
-This is cool!
Awesome!
You should be able to figure out
where you sit.
-Wait, you want us to guess where we sit?
-Are these our TJ colors?
-Hold on, but…
-You picked up on it quickly.
-This is Umi's spot.
-This is cute.
-You figured it out right away.
-That seat?
It's our TJ colors.
-Is this my spot?
-Is this right?
Yep. [in English] Have a seat.
-Okay.
-[in Japanese] Yeah. Thank you. Got it.
-Have a seat. Thank you for coming up.
-Thank you, thank you. Okay, okay.
-[in Japanese] I'm happy you're here.
-What's this?
-Mine says, "Pride"?
-There's something written on it.
-[Noel] "Pride."
-Why pride? Is this a message for me?
Well, pride can refer to your ego, but
a pack of lions is also called a pride.
-It can mean "brotherhood."
-Eh!
Is this your message for me?
-[Noel] It is.
-Whoo!
-Here.
-He says, "Here."
Mine says, "Dream."
-[Noel] That's right.
-[Shizu] "Dream"?
[Umi] Yeah.
[Noel] Because you're always
dreaming big, Kaito.
-I get it. These are your messages for us.
-You got it.
-[Shizu] Chaka-chan, what does yours say?
-Mine says…
-"Believe."
-[Shizu] Isn't that wonderful.
[Noel] Chaka never stops believing in us.
-[Umi] These messages…
-Are these your messages for us?
[Noel] Yes, that's right.
-You carved them.
-This is so sweet.
-The carving is…
-Did you work as a stone carver too?
[Noel laughs] You think I worked
around the clock?
Shall we wait for Team B's arrival?
-I like that. I wonder how they're doing.
-Let's wait for them.
We want to know
how you ended up with a part-time job.
Team B will be surprised
when they find out what you've been up to.
I agree. I'm looking forward to
their reactions too.
[Genta] Are we there yet?
[Shime] We should be close.
-What?
[laughs]
-Hey!
-[exclaiming]
-Hey, Machu!
-Look, Machu's driving!
-Are you really gonna park there?
-Can they make it? I don't know, guys.
[Genta, Machu, Shime] Yay!
-Long time no see!
-[in English] What's up? What's up?
Oh, yay, Noel.
Oh, yeah!
Yeah! Oh, yeah!
-Oh, yeah!
-Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
-I'm so happy.
-[laughing]
I can't believe this.
I'm so happy to see you guys!
-This is wonderful.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
-Feels like I haven't seen you for a year!
-It's been a while, folks!
-Nice, nice.
-It's been forever!
Crap, I can't hold back my tears.
Seriously, I'm gonna cry.
[Shime] Feels like it's been a whole year!
Someone's emotional.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
This is crazy! This is too much!
We've been apart for a week.
[all exclaiming]
[in English] Oh, yeah! Oh, yeah!
Yay, yay, yay, yay! TJ! TJ! TJ! TJ!
[in Japanese] Holy cow.
I really missed you guys.
-This is crazy.
-Oh, yeah.
-What's this?
-It's cute.
-[Noel] Read it.
-[Shizu] Go ahead, Gen-chan.
This is way too peaceful.
[in English] "Peace"!
-[in Japanese] It's adorable.
-It's cute.
[in English] Peace! Double peace!
-Double peace.
-[in Japanese] What?
-What, what?
-What does it say?
Mine says, "Joy."
[all, in English] "Joy."
-"Smile." Yeah!
-[all] "Smile."
-[in Japanese] How cute.
-[Shime] Isn't it sweet?
[Machu] Cute.
Wait, what's this? What is it?
You see, there are
lots of rocks all over Sedona.
-It's a power type.
-Yeah. I looked for the rocks with words
that perfectly describe
each of you and bought these.
-[Machu] Man, this makes me smile.
-[laughs]
-[Shime] What a cute idea.
-[Machu] Really?
-[Genta] It's adorable.
-[Shime] Right?
This is so sweet.
Thank you, this is so thoughtful.
-I'm glad you like it.
-Thank you.
-It's so cute.
-What would be your word, Noel?
-Good question.
-Mine would be…
-[in English] "Love."
-[all exclaiming]
Love, love, love.
[in Japanese] As much as I'd like
to jump right into catching up,
I've gotta prep something really quick.
Wait here.
-All right. Okay, okay.
-Just for a minute.
-You'll be back shortly, yeah?
-Then… We've gotta…
-We'll go get ready too. We'll be quick.
-What? What're you getting ready for?
Now we look like the selfish ones
who didn't bring anything.
What're they gearing up to do?
We didn't prepare anything.
We have our souvenirs. It's okay.
[laughing]
-[Genta] Did he really?
-[Umi] He said…
-[Shizu] I did not.
-You got red in the face.
-Knock it off.
-[Shizu] I said no such thing.
[band members exclaiming]
-This is super! It's the best! Clap you!
-Thank you for waiting.
This is fantastic! Clap, clap!
It's the best!
-[Umi] Tacos!
-[Genta] Yumilicious!
-I practiced hard to make these for you.
-What?
-You made these?
-Are you serious?
-[Noel] Dead serious.
-No way!
-You really made these?
-I've worked here for the past week.
-Oh, what?
-Like, actually?
-[Shime] Wait, seriously? Really?
-What are you up to? That's too funny.
I practiced hard because I wanted you
to enjoy the food I made. Please enjoy.
-You crack me up, man!
-I'm ready to dig in.
Hold on, you're saying you took orders
from the people here, and…
-I did.
-That's awesome.
-Right.
-Is that… why you've got that shirt on?
I worked here.
I trained at this taco truck.
Then these are Noel Tacos.
Welcome to Noel Tacos.
You mean, for the last few days,
you were a tacos chef,
-not a Travis Japan member?
-Yes, I was a tacos chef. Tacos chef…
[Genta] It's working up my appetite.
Speaking of Travis Japan, let's kick off
with a cheer. We'll toast to this.
-[Umi] By the way, what is it?
-[Genta] What is it?
-Tequila.
-Tequila!
-Amigo! Amigo!
-Amigo!
-I'll fill your glasses.
-Oh, wait. It's in a special bottle.
-Wow!
-[laughing]
Awesome!
-[Genta] This is awesome!
-Look at its color.
-The color is amazing.
-The container is cute too.
Whatever that container's supposed to be,
it sure is cute.
-[laughs]
-Whoa!
Oh, yeah. Thank you.
-[Machu] Thanks.
-[exclaiming]
-Hold on, Noel.
-[Shime] Sorry.
Here.
[Shime] Thank you!
-I've got it.
-Oh, really?
[all exclaiming]
Okay, Chaka-chan.
Care to lead us, like usual?
To our reunion…
[laughs]
To our reunion.
-[in English] Cheers!
-[all] Cheers!
Travis Japan!
[cheering]
[all] Amigo!
-Yum.
-Wicked!
-[Umi] Now that's refreshing!
-[Genta] Oh, yum.
-You like it? What a relief.
-This is awesome.
-Bravo.
-[Genta] Bravo!
That was too close. I don't know why,
but I started tearing up.
No, no, no.
-Shall we dig in?
-Yeah?
-Let's dig in.
-Bon Appétit!
[band members] Thanks for the meal!
Digging in!
-Hold on. Wait…
-[Shime] I'm over the moon.
[laughing] Go, go!
[Noel laughs]
-You can't beat this.
-[Shizu] You're scarfing it down!
[laughing]
-[Shizu] You sure look happy.
-Well, time for me to chow down!
-I'm digging in!
-Delicioso.
[Shizu] Go for it.
[laughing]
-Yum!
-Time to give it a whirl.
-[Shime] Yum!
-[laughs]
-You're a genius taco chef!
-I'm glad.
-Time to dig in.
-This is serious deliciousness.
Yum!
-[Shizu] Yum!
-What a decadent meal.
[Machu, laughing] Yum!
[in English] Check it out!
[in Japanese] Mind if we share our spoils?
-What?
-[Genta] It's a bit…
[band members] What is it?
Ta-da!
[Chaka] Are those beer cans?
[Genta] Ta-da!
[Noel] What is it?
[Genta, Machu] Ta-da!
-[Genta] There. Ta-da!
-[Machu] Ta-da!
We visited a brewery
and sampled a variety of beers.
We then picked out drinks
that suit each member.
-That's right, we picked out your drinks.
-Hold up! You drank?
-I… did.
-[band members] What?
-He had a sip!
-[band members cheer]
[Machu] Shime had beer.
-Good job!
-It was delicious.
-[Shizu] Nice!
-[Umi] That's nuts.
It wasn't a whole glass or anything.
The brewery lets you try beer
right off the tap.
I had a tiny sip of it.
But it was out of this world.
-They had something like that?
-All sorts of drinks.
-[Machu] This one's for Noel.
-[Noel] Thanks.
[Chaka] American brewery.
-"Southwest coast."
-Yep.
[Machu] Right. Here's Chaka's.
-[in English] IPA.
-Thank you so much.
[in Japanese] The one in front…
There it is. Here's Umi's.
-Thanks.
-[Genta, in English] Oh, yes.
[in Japanese] Then… Shizuya,
we weren't sure which one you'd like,
so we got you two.
-How thoughtful of you.
-That's considerate. You're a genius.
-That's why there are eight cans.
-[Machu] Exactly.
-I gotta have both then.
-[laughs]
We've hardly had any drinks this trip.
Really?
[Shizu] Yum.
-[Chaka] Delicious.
-[Umi] Good stuff.
[Chaka] That's heavenly.
This is delicious!
-[Machu] It's good, right? Right? Right?
-[cheering]
[Umi] My hands are filthy right now.
Sorry, guys.
-You've got filthy hands!
-Yum.
The drinks go well with the tacos.
-Right?
-Yep, yep, yep, yep.
-We went to a town called Durango.
-That's right. Durango.
Team B isn't done yet!
[Noel] What? You're kidding!
-You're generous.
-Seriously?
-Yep.
-Let's go!
-Thank you, we appreciate it.
-Thank you.
[Shime] We got each of you…
-[Chaka] Is it more beer?
-What is it?
-Beer?
-Doesn't look like it.
-This is for you, Noel.
-Thank you!
-Noel.
-[Chaka] Do we each get one?
-[Genta] Oh, yeah!
-[Umi] I bet it's a beer starter.
-Beer starter? How come?
-[Shime] Zuya-nii.
[Shizu] Here. Thanks.
-[Umi] Craft beer starter. Beer starter!
-[in English] Yeah.
-[Shime, in Japanese] Umi.
-Thank you so much.
We also picked out sachets
that suit each member.
-That makes me smile.
-Chaka.
-[Shime] Open it up, guys.
-[Umi] What's…
-There it is.
-There it is!
-[Noel] It's so pretty!
-[Umi] Wait a minute, Noel.
What? What? What?
-We're matching! [laughs]
-[band members] Matchy-matchy!
[Machu] We're all matchy-matchy!
[Noel] That's darling. Seriously?
[Shime] We picked out stones
that suit each of you.
We decided which ones to get together.
The patterns differ,
but they're all the same type of stone.
-That's right.
-That's what you did?
Yeah. One important thing,
you're supposed to wear it
against your skin. Tuck it in your shirt.
[Noel] I see.
[Genta] Wear it daily,
and it will ward off evil.
That's wonderful.
-I love it.
-It makes me smile.
[Umi] Well, Team A
also has gifts for everyone…
-Yep.
-[Genta] What?
[Chaka] Yes. Shizu, you go first.
Who is it for?
It's for Shime-chan!
[all exclaiming]
-What, what?
-What is it?
-[Chaka] Bubble Wrap.
-Bubble Wrap?
-It will come in handy when you're moving.
-[Shizu] It's a gift for you.
-It's cute!
-[Shizu] Yes. It's a stone bracelet!
-I love it! It's very cute!
-How cute!
-They told us that gemstones carry energy.
-Yes.
Apparently, the stone draws power
from the surrounding elements.
Next is a souvenir from me.
-[Genta] Here comes.
-Chaka-chan!
-My gift is for Genta.
-Thank you very much.
Here you go. Here!
[Machu] Wait…
We each get something different?
We picked out different items
for each of you.
-Hold on.
-What is it?
-I'll open it when I get home.
-How come?
-Open it now! That's the whole point.
-Come on, open it now.
-[Chaka] Now's the time. Right now!
-You're an eager beaver.
[Genta] Oh, wait!
-This rocks! What the heck?
-[Chaka laughs] It's a dream catcher.
-Whoa, this is so cute!
-[Shime] It's cute.
They gave me a refresher on
what a dream catcher does.
The threaded part is called a "spiderweb."
-The middle?
-The web catches your nightmares.
That's why it's best to
hang it in your bedroom.
Then, do you see the rope
attached at the top?
-This part?
-[Umi] Yep.
[Chaka] The more nightmares it catches,
the more good luck it gives you.
So hang it in your bedroom,
and it will get rid of bad energy.
It will bring you good luck.
That's what they said.
Thanks. I've been thinking about
getting one.
-[Chaka] Actually?
-[Shizu] What?
-[Chaka] Was it a perfect gift for you?
-It was.
This one's for Kura.
-What? I've no idea what it could be.
-Oh, yeah!
-[Umi] You'll find out when you open it.
-Okay.
-[Chaka] It's just the gift for Machu.
-Whoa, this is chunky.
-[Machu] What?
-What is it?
[laughs]
[laughing]
-[Genta] Oh, you…
-[Shizu] What is it? You like it or not?
-[band members laugh]
-The heck is this?
[Umi] This object? Well…
[Chaka] The shopkeeper helped Kaito
pick it out.
It's a pot.
-[Machu] A pot?
-Yep. It's a pot.
Yes, it's a clay pot. Let me explain.
It's a one of a kind.
Okay.
This artist is based in Monument Valley.
They design each pot
and paint all of them by hand.
-I see.
-That's incredible.
-I feel so special.
-[Genta] It's cute.
It's a handmade pot created
by a local artist, right?
It's imbued with energy.
Whoa, thanks a ton.
-It suits you. It suits your hat too.
-It really does.
What a perfect gift.
-This will look great in my house.
-[Umi] Please put it up on display.
-[Chaka] That's all the souvenirs from us.
-Yep.
-What about mine?
-What?
-We forgot. Just kidding, we didn't!
-Really?
-The three of us picked this out for you.
-Thank you.
-[Chaka] Here you go.
-[Umi] Then…
[Shizu] This is for you.
-Thank you. What is it?
-I'm dying to know!
-[Shime] What is it?
-[Noel] Ready?
-Go for it.
-[Noel] Ta-da.
-Whoa! Kitty cats!
-[Machu] Oh, how cute.
-[Noel] Aw, cute.
-[Shime] They're adorable.
-Are those turquoises I see?
-[Machu] Look at their eyes.
Turquoises are embedded in it.
[Chaka] These are also
handmade Native American decors.
How do I put it? It may not be a pot, but
it's still a type of handmade ceramics.
-I love it. Thank you.
-[Shime] It's darling.
-[Genta] It's very cute.
-Whoa, I love it. Thank you.
-Thank you.
-Seriously, though. Thanks.
Glad you like your gift.
Well, I was hoping to hear
how the trip went for each of you.
-You visited all sorts of places.
-We sure did.
Perhaps you even visited places
I've never been.
Right, right.
So now, I want to hear about
the memorable moments from your trips.
-I'd love to tell you mine. We really…
-Me too.
We immersed ourselves in the traditions
and the culture everywhere we went.
Taking it all in made me incredibly happy.
I'm glad you feel that way.
The fact that you planned it
made it even more special.
That's great to hear. And now that we've
gathered together, we can talk about it.
-Right?
-For sure.
Like I said, I want to hear all about
the awesome moments.
-That's true.
-[Genta] Great idea.
I want to hear what you felt
and learned on this trip.
-I see.
-[Machu] Of course you do.
-Shizuya, wanna start us off?
-Should I?
Well, let's see. Our trip was focused on
the United States' natural landscapes.
-[Machu] Okay.
-It was all about nature.
-Right. And…
-[Genta] Okay, okay.
How do I say this? Well…
I was hit by the majestic force of nature.
The raw power of the land, so to speak.
We hiked up mountains too.
Ah, of course.
[Shizu] Yeah, we did that.
And then we met the Navajo.
-[Chaka] That's right.
-[Shizu] Which is a Native Tribe.
We had many wonderful encounters
with people and nature alike.
[Chaka] We encountered
a completely foreign culture.
Yes, it was a culture
we've never seen before.
And we also rode horses.
[Shime] Really?
Horseback riding was a blast.
[Genta] How nice.
[Shizu] We had a great experience
with animals too.
-We touched life itself.
-[Shizu] Exactly.
-[Genta] I love that.
-[Machu] It sounds fantastic.
[Noel] Umi, what about you?
-[Umi] Oh, this trip was a blast.
-I was pretty worried about you.
-[Shizu] How come?
-[Umi] Why?
You aren't the type to venture out
into the wilderness.
That's what we said about ourselves
at the start of the trip.
[Noel] That's why I intentionally chose
the RV for Team A.
I based the whole trip around Kaito.
Every experience was chosen
with him in mind.
-We wondered why nature was our theme.
-[Shizu] Yeah, we talked about that.
In the beginning, we did. Hmm.
We thought it was
because the three of us are homebodies.
Yeah, we're homebodies.
But as we stepped into the great outdoors
and became one with nature…
and listened
to the Navajo people's stories…
we realized
there's so much we've yet to learn.
The Natives, who call themselves the Diné,
performed a special dance for us.
-[Machu] Whoa.
-[Shime] Yeah.
The performance is solely composed of
voice, percussion, and dance.
-[Genta] Huh.
-[Umi] Yeah.
The performance represents things
found in nature,
-such as horses or crows.
-[Genta] Whoa.
[Umi] As we watched the dance, we could
really tell the elements it represented.
Yes. At times, the dance resembled horses,
and at others, birds.
It was a reminder that you can enchant
an audience with something so simple.
I wanted to share
their powerful expression with everyone.
[Noel] Of course. I'm glad to hear that.
-Something about the mountain got to him.
-It called out to him.
[Shizu] Umi left us in the dust
and hiked up on his own!
-I didn't expect that.
-He zoomed past us.
[Shime] Did he really?
[Chaka] Noel, you mentioned
you were worried about Kaito.
But Kaito and nature, well…
It was almost like
he was conversing with nature.
Mmm, mmm.
Chaka, do you ever get on the move
seeking breathtaking landscapes?
[Chaka] Usually no. I don't go seeking
beautiful scenery on my own either.
[Machu] Right.
[Chaka] But the view was fantastic.
Really, it blew me away.
Words cannot describe
the magnificent views we encountered.
[Genta] Yeah.
[Chaka] It also can't describe
that we were awestruck.
[Shizu] It's true.
Words can't quite capture it.
Still, I'm grateful
we had this experience.
Also, it's been a while
since it was just the three of us.
[Genta] Yeah, we have our powerhouses,
Chaka, Umi, and Shizu.
You guys are powerhouses?
I thought about
how Travis Japan got started.
As you know, Shime and Noel were the older
members when the band was first formed.
The three of us, well… Travis Japan
started out with five members.
But the three of us
were always together at first.
Some moments on this trip
reminded me of those early days.
It also brought back memories of
Shizu and Umi from that time too.
The three of us have always worked hard.
And it was rewarding
to travel with them again.
We were stoked the entire trip. Like,
it's not that we've become besties, but…
-We tried to be considerate, yeah.
-The trip deepened our friendship.
But looking back and comparing it to now…
it was always the three of us
every step of the way.
And now, I hope the seven of us
can discover new sceneries together.
You know what? Hearing all this
makes me happy. It really does.
These three have adapted to nature
more than they realize.
-[chuckling] It's true.
-I'm glad.
-Thanks. I'm glad. Nice.
-[Umi] No, I had a lot of fun. Thanks.
-[Machu] How nice. Team A.
-[Shime] That was wonderful.
Machu, your turn.
-Actually, I want to hear from Genta.
-[Genta] Oh, sure. Okay.
Machu probably took away
the most from this trip.
-[Genta] It's true.
-That's what I think.
Well, I've always had a fascination
for Native American culture and designs.
On the trip, we saw many handmade crafts.
For instance,
we'd ask all about the artists
behind rugs, cushions,
and gem-studded jewelry.
There was so much
we gained from their stories.
Encountering culture and values
so different from Japan's
sent a shock right through me.
But like I said,
I love the Native American culture.
I thoroughly enjoyed immersing myself
in the local culture
and learning the history of the
United States through the locals' tales.
More than anything,
we've always worked together,
but I'd often find myself wondering
what the rest of you were doing.
We'd joke and say, "Do you think Zuya-nii…
-[laughing]
-…is being a Debbie Downer?"
We did say that, yeah.
Like, "Maybe Zuya-nii's at it,"
or like Noel said,
"Is Umi okay being out in the wild?"
Personally, I thought, "Chaka may
not find the scenery so striking."
I also thought Noel must be
going through a lot,
though I've no idea what's on his mind.
Especially because
you came up with this trip.
You probably had your reasons.
You may even have had expectations for us.
I'm sure things haven't been easy for you.
You must have a lot on your mind.
Even still, Travis Japan
never left my mind during the entire trip,
no matter where I was or what I was doing.
I'm grateful for TJ,
and I'm happy to be a part of it.
Now that our trip is over,
and we visited many different places,
I can proudly say I love TJ.
-[Chaka] Shime, what about you?
-[Shizu] Shime's next.
-[Chaka] I'd love to hear your thoughts.
-For me, well…
Well, it was so much fun.
I don't even know where to start.
-[Genta] Right.
-[Shime] We boarded a train.
You mean the Durango Silverton
Narrow Gauge Railroad.
-[Genta] Durango, yep.
-It was such a great experience.
The scenery we saw
from the train was just fantastic.
[Machu] It was great.
[Shime] It's like Big Thunder Mountain
in real life.
-[Machu] We're not even exaggerating.
-[Shime] It's not an attraction.
The city is like a theme park
brought to life.
The entire ride lasted about two hours.
Well, I can be a bit of a worrywart,
but during the train ride,
I kept thinking,
-"Why worry about every little thing?"
-[Machu] Mm-hmm.
And that was… Well…
it was a great experience for me.
-I see.
-[Shime] Yeah. That was…
-What did you think of Team B, Shime?
-The Team B trio.
We picked roles for the trip.
-[Shizu] What?
-[Noel] You did?
[Umi] Oh, really. Tell us about it.
What was it? Machu was
our designated driver and cameraman.
-He was your cameraman and the chauffeur.
-[Chaka] You had roles, I see.
-Machu did, yeah.
-Yeah.
Then, Gen-chan was in charge of
enjoying everything that came our way.
-He was the team cheerleader.
-The cheerleader, yeah.
[Genta] I tried to make everything fun.
-Easy.
-It's a perfect role for Genta.
-It was…
-An easy role to fill.
-[Shizu] The easiest one, huh?
-[Genta] Whatever.
-Then, Shime? What was your role?
-I was the group leader.
-The leader?
-[Machu] Yeah, Shime was our leader.
Shime, you're Team B's leader?
-He's the senior member out of us three.
-Yup.
[Genta] Shime is our leader.
-I'm usually never in a leadership role.
-[Chaka, Umi] Right.
-I had no idea what I was supposed to do.
-[Chaka] Yeah.
I thought, "Should I do
something special as the leader?
Should I try to be in charge?"
But in the end, I realized,
"No, I shouldn't worry about it too much."
[Machu chuckles]
The opposite of what you'd expect.
That's right,
the leader doesn't have to do anything.
Whatever, look at
how much you're shouldering!
[Shime] That was poorly worded.
It's not that leaders don't do anything.
It's about teamwork.
I had to let go of things
that were outside of my control.
Yeah.
But in those moments,
I had Machu and Genta to fall back on.
There were also times
when I had to step up and make decisions.
I learned the importance of interpersonal
relationships. There's a balance to it.
[Shizu] Right. The leader is the glue
that holds the group together.
-[Chaka] Noel, I bet you're over the moon.
-I really am.
I was so worried about you, Shime.
-[Shizu laughs]
-[Machu] Really, now?
I couldn't decide whether grouping
Machu and Genta together was a good idea.
Since Genta is already interested in
the Native American culture,
I thought Machu would be
a fun addition to the mix.
But then, I wasn't sure
how Shime would mesh with those two.
You know, Shime can be
a bit of an overthinker.
-Yeah.
-He tends to overanalyze everything.
I don't think it's a fault by any means,
but I was worried that Shime would be
self-conscious about his sensitive side.
[Shime] Right, right, right.
I hoped you'd open your mind…
-[Shime] Yeah. Mm-hmm.
-…even by a bit, on this trip.
What you said makes me really happy.
I learned to be more open to uncertainty.
-[Noel] I'm glad.
-Yep.
Let me tell you, he's a good leader.
-[band members] Yeah?
-He's a comforting presence.
[Genta] Comforting… He's a peacekeeper.
-He was a great leader.
-[Shime] You mean it?
[band members laugh]
-He downed his glass!
-He chugged it!
-[Machu] That was tequila!
-TJ's leader downed his drink!
Well, honestly, Chaka wasn't much of
a leader for us, but he did all right.
[band members laugh]
-Is that supposed to make me feel better?
-He's so bad at comforting people, huh?
-I'm in pure bliss.
-Come on, everyone…
[Chaka] We want to hear
your experience now.
-[Chaka] You're the poet among us.
-Very true.
[Chaka] I'd love to hear your thoughts.
Well… It was so much fun,
and I learned a bunch.
Genta and Shime touched on it,
but there's a lot you never learn
unless you go out
and experience things firsthand.
Hmm.
Then… how do I put it?
Let's see…
-And… Nope, I'm not gonna cry. Nope.
-[Umi] You're gonna cry.
It's like…
[Chaka] It's okay to cry.
We're all sharing fond memories.
What do I even say…
Simply put, on day one,
we said we wanted to find out
why Noel chose the three of us as Team B
by the end of the trip.
To be completely honest, on day one,
we couldn't tell you.
[Shime] Right.
But it'd be nice if we can get to
the bottom of why you planned this trip.
But to be honest,
I still don't have an answer for you.
Well, that's fine.
I can't tell you what Noel wanted,
but on this trip,
we had so many wonderful encounters.
You can't learn about a different culture
unless you go and experience it firsthand.
That's my takeaway from this trip.
The only way to learn
is through encounters.
As important as it is
to learn about different cultures,
we were also deeply touched by
the kindness of all the locals
we met along the way.
Right.
[Machu] Anyhow, it was
a heartwarming trip. That's for sure.
I don't even know
what I was getting at anymore.
-What's wrong with that?
-[Noel] Machu, you…
-You had many wonderful experiences.
-I thought that's where you'd land, Machu.
[band members] Right.
I know we all have
our personal ambitions and goals,
but I also know
just how tender-hearted you are, Machu.
I knew it'd take you some time
to find an answer
while you experience
so many new things at once.
You'll take your time
processing everything,
but eventually, you'll find your answer.
Then, you'll push forward
and pave your own path.
I know that's who you are, Machu.
[♪ gentle music playing]
I figured you'd be the last one
to find your answer.
So you don't need to
give us an answer now.
You don't have to know…
Machu, you don't have to know
what this trip meant for you right away.
Actually, that's very like you.
[Genta, Shime] Right, right.
I hope some day,
when you look back on this trip,
you can say it was a good experience.
It may have been Team B's experience,
but at the same time,
this is your experience, Machu.
Hopefully, the answer you reach
will include all seven of us somehow.
[Machu, voice breaking] But…
we parted ways and learned a ton.
It was such a lighthearted, fun trip.
We've been together since day…
the entire time, we…
-[Genta imitates Machu] Day…
-[band members laugh]
It was so fun, and we talked a ton,
and we learned a bunch of fun things.
We guessed what you wanted us
to learn on this trip.
Well, we saw so many
breathtaking landscapes.
But there's one thing I can say for sure.
I felt so at ease
when I finally saw everyone again.
-Oh, you…
-[Chaka] Stop talking.
[Genta] Stop it. Don't talk anymore.
[Umi] But because we went on this trip,
we can talk so openly
about how we feel right now.
-[Genta, chuckling] Umi's crying!
-[band members laugh]
[Genta] Umi's crying in front of people…
[Chaka] It's a bit…
[Genta] Chaka's tearing up too.
[Chaka] Oh, man, how do I say this,
I'm touched by everything you just said.
Distance made my heart grow fonder for TJ.
We had all these wonderful experiences
with our teams.
But Noel, he was on his own this time.
We don't know everything he's done for us.
All we can do is keep trying to guess
why he sent us on this trip.
But Noel's, well…
How Noel feels is the most…
Right?
[Chaka] There must be a lot
going through your head right now.
After all, we were apart for a while.
Could you tell us your thoughts?
-I just wonder, what was the point?
-[Umi] Yeah, we'd like to hear from you.
We're not asking you
to give us all the answers.
I'll be frank.
I don't have an answer for you.
Each of you brings
a unique personality to Travis Japan.
Everything we've accomplished is
because of what you bring to the table.
You're the parts
that make Travis Japan whole.
So, there isn't a single answer
I could give you.
I don't know…
I don't quite know how to say this.
Anyway, I also had time to reflect
while we were apart.
I thought, I want Travis Japan
to be the seven of us.
And the times we spend together are
the most precious moments of my life.
That's why I want
to keep doing this with you.
The time we spend looking after
one another is important too,
but when we grouped up,
it gave everyone some time to reflect.
I thought we can become
more united as a band
if each of us brings back the answers
we found to Travis Japan.
When you shared your experiences just now,
it showed me
that you didn't squander the vacation.
Each of you tried to
tie meanings to the trip,
and reflected on how you can better
contribute to Travis Japan.
I'm so happy that this trip
wasn't lost on any of you.
And maybe, that's the answer
I was hoping to find for Travis Japan.
-I'm overcome with joy.
-[Chaka] Mmm.
I'm glad I had the chance to think about
what I can do for everyone,
and hopefully I showed you
what I want to bring to Travis Japan.
I sincerely wish for the seven of us
to continue setting forth on adventures
as Travis Japan. [sniffles]
Man, was it the time of our lives,
or what?
-Well… we're not out of time yet, are we?
-That's right.
-Our journey will go on.
-Yeah.
Exactly. Our trip isn't over yet.
[Genta] Our trip isn't over?
We're not done just yet.
-We're finally together.
-We're all together after all this time.
-That's right, finally, we've…
-[Chaka] Oh, but…
-You've only been on the road for a week.
-[band members] That's right.
[Genta] But I really missed you guys
after just a week.
Let's do the cheer.
Then, we'll plan tomorrow's trip.
That's right,
we'll create a plan together.
The trip isn't over yet.
-We've got some time left!
-This is a story you two started.
Machu.
It's thanks to you
that we have our special cheer.
Noel, why don't you lead us?
To our next adventure.
Well, Travis Japan, um…
We've got no time… [sniffles]
…to be a-wasting.
I mean it when I say we'll be together
until we're as wrinkled as prunes.
We'll bring back what we learned
to Travis Japan.
We'll embark on many, many more
spectacular journeys together. Agreed?
[all] Agreed!
Let's go, TJ! Let's go!
[all] Thank you! [chuckle]
Translated by Megumi Hunter